Are you serious?
What, scared?
Shu Tinglan,
you've really been brainwashed
by Lin Zhinan.
How could you lose your head
and do something so crazy?
I wasn't supposed to see him tonight.
I thought I'd dodge the class reunion,
only to run into him on the street.
Never expected it
to be Zhuo Yu'an.
After all these years,
he still remembers me.
[Unsoiled Starlight]
[Episode 1]
[Adapted from Migu's novel
"Unsoiled Starlight"]
[Original Auther: Shan Gu Jun]
[Three hours ago]
To our cooperation!
-To our cooperation!
Cheers to our cooperation!
I negotiated this case myself,
but she took all the credit.
Mr. Chen.
One more toast to you!
Here, let me top you up.
Maybe,
toasting counts more than real work.
You're Ms. Shu, right?
She's Shu Tinglan.
Do you know the secret to surviving
as an independent woman at work?
It's knowing when to bend.
In a situation like this,
you have to drink!
Mr. Chen,
let me toast you.
That's more like it.
Come on!
Here's to independent women!
[Zhuoyuan Technology's
New Product Launch]
Welcome, everyone,
to Zhuoyuan Technology's
new product launch.
Nice to see you.
I'm Zhuo Yu'an.
[Zhuoyuan Technology's
New Product Launch]
Hello.
Zhinan.
Hey,
Shu Tinglan,
are you coming to the reunion tonight?
I've got a difficult client.
I probably can't make it.
Then take care.
Handle it or give up.
Yeah, I know.
It's so noisy over there.
Hey, hurry up.
Zhuo Yu'an will be here too.
Isn't he your high school crush?
What are you talking about?
Don't mind him.
Come on. I'm hanging up.
Let's go.
What nonsense are you talking?
Come join us!
Tinglan,
you're really not coming?
I'm not.
Have fun.
How am I supposed to face you?
Tired, smelling of alcohol,
and down on my luck,
my life feels dead and stuck,
while you're still as dazzling as ever.
Our paths won't cross again.
Am I right,
Zhuo Yu'an?
Mr. Zhuo!
Mr. Zhuo, can we have a quick word?
Mr. Zhuo, please wait!
Mr. Zhuo, please answer a few questions!
Just a few words!
Please, say something!
Mr. Zhuo!
Jiajia.
You're my pick on your team.
Thank you, Mr. Chen.
-Let me get the car door for you.
-Let's drink again.
Jiajia,
see you next time.
Okay.
-Bye, Mr. Chen.
-Take care, Mr. Chen.
Deng.
[No cars available]
Little thing.
Why are you all alone here,
just like me?
Zhuo Yu'an?
Zhuo Yu'an!
Thanks!
It's snowing.
It's hard to get a cab here.
I'll give you a ride.
Get in.
What, am I your cab driver?
Take the front seat.
Where to?
47 Yongan East Road.
Thanks, Mr. Zhuo.
That's a little formal.
I was afraid you wouldn't remember me.
After all...
I remember you.
We were at the same high school.
Shu Tinglan.
I saw you wrestling
with that trash bag earlier.
Yeah.
I mistook it for a kitten.
You like cats?
Not particularly.
But I couldn't just ingore it
since.. since I saw it.
Yeah.
Exactly.